keepyourbookmarks.info 2015-05-23

# Vibin.FM - Privacy Policy

### Protecting your private information is our priority. 

This Statement of Privacy applies to the http://vibin.fm and Vibin.FM and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Vibin.FM include http://vibin.fm, https://vibin.fm, https://vibin.fm, https://www.vibin.fm, Vibin.FM, www.vibin.fm, VibinFM, and Vibin FM. The Vibin.FM website is a Online Electronic Music site. By using the Vibin.FM website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.   

### Collection of your Personal Information 

Vibin.FM may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Vibin.FM. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Vibin.FM website. 

Vibin.FM encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Vibin.FM so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Vibin.FM is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Vibin.FM website. 

Use of your Personal Information Vibin.FM collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. Vibin.FM may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Vibin.FM and its affiliates. Vibin.FM may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. 

Vibin.FM does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Vibin.FM may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. Vibin.FM may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Vibin.FM, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

Vibin.FM may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Vibin.FM, in order to determine what Vibin.FM services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Vibin.FM to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. Vibin.FM will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Vibin.FM or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Vibin.FM; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Vibin.FM, or the public. 

### Security of your Personal Information 

Vibin.FM secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. 

### Children Under Thirteen 

Vibin.FM does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

### Disconnecting your Vibin.FM Account from Third Party Websites 

You will be able to connect your Vibin.FM account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR VIBIN.FM ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. Users may learn how to disconnect their accounts from third-party websites by logging out. Users may also contact us via email.. 

### Changes to this Statement 

Vibin.FM will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Vibin.FM encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Vibin.FM is protecting your information. 

### Contact Information 

Vibin.FM welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Vibin.FM has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Vibin.FM at: 

### Vibin.FM 

Detroit, Michigan   
Email Address: info@vibin.fm 

Effective as of January 01, 2015
